myaccess.com 2008-06-11

# Corporate - Privacy Policy :: Vantage Learning

Login to: 

Vantage Learning  
110 Terry Drive, Suite 100  
Newtown, PA 18940

800.230.2213 

215.579.8391 

**Personal Information**

When you visit any of the Vantage Learning websites you remain anonymous. Access to some areas of the site may require registration. When required, we will tell you why we want the information and how we plan to use it. You may choose whether to access pages that require registration. We may ask you for your name, e-mail address, and other basic information. That data will always remain protected, and we will never add you to e-mail lists unless you make a specific request. We will use any information we gather only to help us understand your needs and make our website or products more valuable to you. We will not provide any personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission. We will always give you the option to elect not to receive additional information from us during the registration process. If you sign up for any of our electronic newsletters, you will find "unsubscribe" instructions readily available in every newsletter. 

**Protecting Your Privacy**

Vantage Learning takes every step possible to protect your privacy at all times. We also enable security measures to protect personal information in storage. We will not provide any personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission. Some areas of our website provide links to third-party sites. Vantage Learning staff members review these sites to ensure their "safety"; however, because we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third-party sites. 

**Cookies**

Some areas of the Vantage Learning website may use cookies to help you customize your experience at our site. These cookies do not track individual information for marketing purposes, and we will not contact you without your consent. A cookie stores useful information that lets us remember you when you return. Cookies from these sites can be read and processed only by Vantage Learning servers. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of the website. 

**Questions**

Vantage Learning welcomes comments and questions regarding this privacy policy. Our staff is dedicated to protecting your personal information and makes every effort to keep this information secure. You may direct any questions about Vantage Learning's privacy policy to [webmaster@vantagelearning.com](mailto:webmaster@vantagelearning.com).
